As times change, difficult cases will increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is a sports club!
!مسرح اليوم هو نادي رياضة
Let's train both our minds and bodies!
!لنمرّن أجسادنا وأذهاننا
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
After winning a raffle, we were invited to a sports gym
بعد فوزنا في إحدى السحوبات، تمّت دعوتنا
the day before its grand re-opening.
لصالة رياضية في اليوم السابق لإعادة افتتاحها العظيم
I-- I can't go on...
...لا-لا أستطيع الاستمرار
I'm exhausted... I can't move...
أنا مُرهق... التحرّك مستحيل
How pathetic.
هذا بائس
Your booze and lack of exercise has gotten to you!
نال منك الخمر وقلّة التمرين يا أبي
Don't be stupid!
!حمقاء
Detectives fight from the neck up!
!يقاتل المتحرّيون من أعناقهم فأعلى
More like from the neck down in your case...
من العنق فأسفل في حالتك
These renovations have been the earnest wish of our sports club!
كانت التجديدات جلّ أمل نادينا الرياضي
As a former high-diver,
بصفتي غطّاسة ارتفاعات سابقة
I really understand the greatness of sports!
أعي عظمة الرياضات جيّداً
So it was my hope to help others get in shape and better their health...
لذا تمنّيتُ مساعدة الآخرين في اكتساب اللياقة وتحسين صحّتهم
Hey, Conan-kun.
اسمع يا كونان-كن
Let's ditch my dad and check out the pool!
لنترك أبي ونذهب لرؤية المسبح
Yeah!
!أجل
The glass exterior is so wonderful!
الحائط الزجاجي جميل جدّاً
They're doing high-diving up there!
!يقومون بغوص مرتفع هناك
That's a high-diver from this club;
إنّه غطّاس ارتفاعات من هذا النادي
I think his name is Saijo-san!
أظنّ اسمه كان سايجو-سان
High-Dive Competitor Saijo Naoya
سايجو ناويا غطّاس ارتفاع
You're up, Naruse! Don't mess up now!
!دورك يا ناروسي! لا تخفق
What was that?!
!ما كان ذلك؟
And you wanna be team captain, Naruse?!
!وتريد أن تكون قائداً يا ناروسي؟
High-Dive Competitor Naruse Keiichi
غطّاس ارتفاع ناروسي كييتشي
I haven't gotten enough practice with all the preparations lately.
لم أتمّرن بما يكفي مع تحضيرات الافتتاح مؤخراً
That the only reason you haven't practiced enough?
أهذا السبب الوحيد لعدم تمرّنك حقاً؟
What's that supposed to mean?!
!ما قصدك؟
In any case, diving like that,
...أيّاً يكن، بقفزك ذاك
it's clear how the tournament'll turn out.
نتيجة المسابقة واضحة لي
W-What did you say?!
!ما-ماذا؟
Stop it, you two!
توقّفا
There are people here! And the media!
!يوجد ناس! الإعلام أيضاً
You sure you should be acting all big, Kijima?
أيجدر بك التصرّف بتعالٍ حقّاً يا كيجيما؟
I-- I'm not trying to act big...
لا-لا أحاول التصرّف بتعالٍ
Competitive Swimmer Kijima Hisashi
سبّاح كيجيما هيساشي
With that lame earring...
...مع أقراطك السخيفة هذه
Are you really fit to boss people around?
أتظن أنّك ملائم لتأمر الآخرين حقّاً؟
Hey, Naruse! Get back to practice!
!ناروسي! لنرجع للتمرين
I think that's Kijima-san, Saijo-san's former rival...
،أظنّ ذاك الشخص كيجيما-سان خصم سايجو-سان السابق
Saijo-san took his place as team captain,
أخذ سايجو-سان مكانه قائداً للفريق
so he switched to competitive swimming...
فانتقل للسباحة التنافسية
Here we have our prized competitive swimming and high-diving pool.
هذا مسبح الغوص المرتفع والسباحة التنافسية الذي نفخر به
They're in the middle of high-dive practice as we speak!
لاعبونا يتمرنون بينما نتكلم
Look out!
!انتبه
I know the tournament's soon, but don't go overboard, Saijo-kun!
!أعرف أنّ المسابقة تقترب، لكن لا تبالغ يا سايجو-كن
You're our ace, you know!
!فأنت نجمنا
I wonder.
أشكّ في ذلك
Your look says, "What a pity he survived."
فملامحك تقول "من المؤسف أنّه نجا" يا سيّدتي المالكة
Oh, you're such a kidder, Saijo-kun!
تحبّ المزاح حقاً يا سايجو-كن
Nothing compared to you, though.
ليس بقدرك
You're low!
!أنت وضيع
I know that you want to say
...أعرف أنّك تريد قول
the re-opening will fail if even a rumor
أنّ إعادة الافتتاح ستفشل لو تسرّبت مجرد إشاعة
hits the media or tax office!
!للإعلام أو مكتب الضرائب
Tax office?
مكتب الضرائب؟
Conan-kun.
كونان-كن؟
What're you doing here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Oh, uhh...
...أنا
Saijo-kun.
سايجو-كن
We're having a job-well-done party in my office at 8:00!
سنُقيم حفلة إتمام العمل في مكتبي عند الثامنة
Don't forget!
لا تنسَ
Well, guess I'll get a little more practice in.
حسناً، لعلّي سأتمرن مزيداً
A hidden camera photo? The man is that Naruse guy...
...صورة كاميرا خفيّة؟ الرجل هو ناروسي ذاك
Hey, you dropped something!
!أسقطت شيئاً
Hey, you dropped this!
سقطت هذه
Oh, sorry. I always wear earplugs during practice, you see.
آسف، أرتدي سدّادات أُذن عند التمرين دوماً
Thanks.
شكراً لك
This is my pay dirt.
هذه تذكرتي المالية
Pay dirt?
تذكرته المالية؟
And another!
!هاك
That smarts...
...مؤلم
You brought it on yourself!
أنت جلبت ذلك على نفسك
You should work out instead of smoking and drinking!
عليك اكتساب لياقة بدل التدخين والشرب دوماً
Yeah, that's about the only thing you have going for you...
صحيح، فهي وحدها ما تتميّز به
But that club sure was great!
لكن كان ذاك النادي رائعاً
Yeah!
أجل
Right, Dad?
أبي
Come on, Dad!
!أبي
Let's see, is it about work?
لنرَ، أهو متعلّق بالعمل؟
Ugh...
...يا إلهي
Mori-kun. It's me, Megure.
موري-كن، إنّه أنا ميغوري
The Inspector?
حضرة المفتش؟
I hate to ask, but could you come to the Saeki Sports Club right away?
اعذرني، لكن هلّا أتيت لنادي سايكي للرياضة فوراً؟
Along with Ran-kun and Conan-kun.
مع ران-كن وكونان-كن
One of the instructors, Saijo Naoya-san,
،وجدنا جثّة أحد المعلّمين، سايجو ناويا-سان
was found dead in the pool!
في المسبح
What?!
!ماذا؟
Inspector!
!حضرة المفتّش
Sorry I'm late. So, what do we have?
نعتذر على التأخير، ما الوضع إذاً؟
It's just as it looks.
كما ترى
We'll need to wait for an autopsy,
علينا انتظار نتائج التشريح
but the estimated time of death
لكن وقت الوفاة المقدّر
is between 8:00 and 9:00 pm.
هو بين الثامنة والتاسعة مساءً
It appears that--
...سبب الوفاة
He drowned.
الغرق، صحيح؟
Just because you've been in water before
مجرد دخولك الماء سابقاً
doesn't make you an expert!
لا يجعلك خبيراً
He's absolutely correct.
معه كلّ الحقّ
After all, the body's condition points entirely to a drowning.
فحالة الجثّة تشير لموتها غرقاً
See the foam coming from his nose and mouth?
أترون الرغوة من أنفه وفمه؟
And the slight bit of blood from his ears.
كما دم قليل من أذنيه
The water in his mouth and nose
سبّب الماء في فمه وأنفه
produced pressure on the inner ears.
ضغطاً على أذنيه الداخليتين
They're both characteristics of a drowning, right?
هذه من خصائص الغرق، صحيح؟
T-That's right, but how did you know that?
أ-أجل، لكن كيف عرفت؟
Eh? Oh, I think it was on a suspense TV show the other day...
ماذا؟ أظنّ رأيتُ ذلك على برنامج إثارة في التلفزيون سابقاً
But he was a professional swimmer.
...لكنه كان سبّاحاً محترفاً، حتّى لو قفز من ارتفاع
It's hard to see him drowning...
يصعب اعتقاد أنّه غرق
Huh? Did he hit his forehead on something?
ماذا؟ هل ارتطمت جبهته بشيء؟
See? There's a mark on his cap!
!انظروا، يوجد أُثر على غطاء رأسه
Exactly. It seems he messed up during his high-diving practice.
تماماً، يبدو أنّه ارتكب خطأً أثناء تمرينه في الغوص المرتفع
I hear it's quite a dangerous practice indeed...
سمعتُ أنّه كان تمريناً خطيراً
I asked you here because you saw him practicing this afternoon,
طلبتُ قدومكم لأنّكم رأيتموه يتمرن ظهيرة اليوم
and I wanted your testimonies.
وأردت شهادتكم
It was a very close call then;
نجا بأعجوبة في تلك المرّة
I guess he wasn't so lucky this time...
لكن يبدو أنّه أخفق تماماً هذه المرة
Say, was there nobody else here?
ألم يكن هناك أحد معه؟
Was Saijo-san practicing alone?
أكان سايجو-سان يتمرّن بمفرده؟
Hey, you! Shut up for a minute!
!أنت! اخرس للحظة
So?
إذاً؟
I'm certain of it.
أنا متأكدة
Everyone else had finished preparing for tomorrow
أنهى البقيّة تحضيراتهم للغد
and were in the back office
وكانوا في المكتب الخلفي
at 8:00 for a job-well-done party.
في حفلة إتمام عمل عند الثامنة
A tournament is coming up,
هناك مسابقة تقترب
so Saijo-san practiced whenever he could.
لذا تمرّن سايجو-سان متى استطاع
Probably tonight, too...
الليلة أيضاً غالباً
We also have a witness. There's no question about it.
لدينا شاهد أيضاً، فلا شكّ بالأمر
A witness?
شاهد؟
Yes. An old man on the second floor of those apartments
أجل، قال رجل مُسنّ يعيش على الطابق الثاني في الشقة المقابلة
says he saw someone doing high-dive practice all alone.
أنّه رأى شخصاً يتمرن على غوص مرتفع بمفرده
But he didn't see the accident itself, right?
لكنّه لم يرَ الحادثة نفسها، صحيح؟
W-Well, no, but...
...حـ-حسناً، كلا، لكن
Shut up!
!اخرس
Say, I think Saijo-san always wore earplugs when practicing.
بالمناسبة، أظنّ سايجو-سان كان يرتدي سدّادات أذن دوماً عند تمرينه
Yes, the examiners removed them earlier...
أجل، خلعها المحللون قبل قليل
Here they are.
ها هي
He had different ones this afternoon.
كان يرتدي سدّادات مختلفة ظهيرة اليوم
Probably switched 'em.
بدّلها غالباً
There's nothing unusual about that!
لا غريب في هذا
Then what about his cap?
ماذا عن غطاء رأسه إذاً؟
What about his cap, Conan-kun?
ما بشأنه يا كونان-كن؟
High-divers don't usually wear caps, you know?
لا يرتدي غطّاسو الارتفاع أغطية رأس عادةً، أليس كذلك؟
So? People can do different things sometimes!
وما في ذلك؟ التغيير بين الحين والآخر طبيعي
Quit looking at every little thing!
!كفّ عن التدقيق على كلّ شيء
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Let him go.
دعيه
Say, was Saijo-san's locker locked?
أكانت خزانة سايجو-سان مقفلة؟
Huh? No, it was unlocked... But who're you, little boy?
...ماذا؟ كلا، كانت مفتوحة لكن من أنت يا صبيّ؟
You know, he's the kid staying with Detective Mori.
إنّه الفتى الذي يقيم مع المتحرّي موري
Oh yeah?
هكذا إذاً
What's this smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
This is chloroform!
!هذا كلوروفورم
No question about it! This was a murder!
!لا شكّ في الأمر! كانت هذه جريمة قتل
A couple details are a bit fuzzy,
هناك بضعة تفاصيل مشوشة
but it appears this was an accident.
لكن يبدو أنّها كانت حادثة
What?! You gotta be kidding me!
!ماذا؟! لا تمازحني
This was clearly a murder!
!هذه جريمة قتل بكلّ وضوح
Thanks for coming, Mori-kun.
شكراً لقدومك يا موري-كن
No, I'm glad I could help, Inspector!
أبداً، يسرّني المساعدة حضرة المفتش
Hold on, now!
مهلاً
Are we just gonna leave like this?!
هل سنغادر هكذا؟
Umm, this won't affect our re-opening tomorrow, will it?
المعذرة، لن يؤثر هذا على إعادة افتتاحنا غداً، صحيح؟
Hmm, well, the police will be finished tonight,
حسناً... يُفترض أن تنتهي إجراءات الشرطة الليلة
so it should be all right.
فلا مشكلة غالباً
Hear that, everyone?
أسمعتم جميعاً؟
What happened to Saijo-kun was terrible,
ما حلّ بسايجو-كن كان فظيعاً
but it was an accident!
لكنّها كانت حادثة مؤسفة
We'll re-open tomorrow as scheduled!
سنُعيد الافتتاح غداً كما المُخطط
Just to be on the safe side, do your final checks--
...أجروا تفقّداتكم الأخيرة من باب الحيطة
Damn! I have to hurry!
!تبّاً! عليّ الإسراع
The incident occurred after we left.
وقعت الحادثة بعدما غادرنا
It would be hard for an outsider to get inside.
سيكون من الصعب تسلّل دخيل
Therefore, it's highly likely that the killer was someone on the inside!
لذا يُرجّح أن القاتل من الداخل
Hey, you guys!
المعذرة
What is it, little boy?
ماذا يا فتى؟
The job-well-done party was here, right?
كانت حفلة إتمام العمل هنا، صحيح؟
Did anyone leave during it?
هل غادر أحد أثناءها؟
I dunno...
...لا أدري
If so, I didn't notice.
لم ألحظ لو حصل ذلك
It was a pretty lively party.
فقد كانت حفلة حيوية
Thank you!
!شكراً لكما
In other words, it wouldn't have been impossible to sneak out.
أي أنّ التسلل خارجاً لم يكن مستحيلاً
Those three who opposed Saijo-san...
...الثلاثة الذين خاصموا سايجو-سان
Saeki Reiko, blackmailed over tax evasion...
سايكي ريكو المُبتزة بتهربها من الضرائب
Kijima Hisashi, who had his leadership position stolen...
وكيجيما هيساشي الذي فقد منصب القائد
Naruse Keiichi, blackmailed with adultery photos...
وناروسي كييتشي المُبتز بصورة العلاقة
The killer is definitely one of them!
القاتل أحدهم بلا شكّ
The problem is that old man's testimony...
...المشكلة هي شهادة المُسن هناك
It greatly hinders my theory...
...إنّها تعيق نظريتي لحدٍّ كبير
Guess I'll have to go there myself!
لا أمامي سوى الذهاب له بنفسي
Yes, little boy?
ماذا يا فتى؟
Hello! My name is Edogawa Conan!
مرحباً، اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
A detective told me to come hear your story.
أخبرني مُتحرٍّ بالذهاب لسماع قصتك
My story?
قصتي؟
You're a painter!
!أنت رسّام
It's just an old man's hobby.
مجرد هواية مُسن
Did you paint this based on what you saw from here?!
أرسمت هذه بناءً على ما رأيته من هنا؟
That's right.
أجل
Painting at a set time everyday is an old man's excitement!
الرسم في وقت محدّد يومياً هي الهواية التي تثير حماس المُسن يومياً
A set time?!
وقت محدّد؟
Yes. I drew that picture tonight, too...
أجل، رسمتُ تلك اللوحة الليلة أيضاً
Saijo-kun, was his name?
كان اسمه سايجو-كن؟
What a pity...
...يا للأسف
Turning off the lights,
،إطفاء الأنوار
practicing intensely... He brought it on himself.
والتمرّن بتهوّر... هو من جلب ذلك على نفسه
He turned off the lights?!
!أطفأ الأنوار؟
Yes. His diving form made a silhouette with the full moon behind him.
أجل، شكّلت هيئة غوصه صورة ظلّية مع القمر المكتمل وراءه
So you didn't actually see Saijo-san's face tonight, then?!
لم ترَ وجه سايجو-سان بالتحديد الليلة إذاً؟
That's right. It was very beautiful...
...كلا، كان مشهداً بغاية الجمال
It sparkled so beautifully...
تلألأ بشكل آخّاذ
The image came right to me so I painted it right away.
تراءت الصورة لي فرسمتُها فوراً
I call it, "Diving Against the Moonlight."
"أطلق عليها "الغوص تحت ضوء القمر
Beautiful? If he hit his head,
،جميل؟ لو ارتطم رأسه
he would've lost his balance and fallen!
!كان ليفقد توازنه ويسقط
This is! Ah, now I get it! That person was the killer!
!هذه... فهمت الآن! القاتل هو ذاك الشخص
Hey, you! Where were you?!
!أنت! أين كنت؟
You had us worried, Conan-kun!
أقلقتنا يا كونان-كن
Uh oh!
!تبّاً
You're in trouble now! Get over here!
!سأعاقبك! تعال
No!
!كلا
Stop! Get back here!
!أنت! توقف
Get back here!
!توقف
Give yourself up!
!استسلم
Sorry, old man!
!آسف يا عمّ
It's my butt today...
...إنّها مؤخرتي اليوم
Are you all right?! Dad! Conan-kun!
!أأنتما بخير؟ أبي! كونان-كن
Ran! Gather everyone here on the double!
ران، استدعي الجميع هنا فوراً
What's this about, Mori-kun?
ما الخطب يا موري-كن؟
I know who's responsible for this incident.
اكتشفت المسؤول عن هذه القضيّة
Responsible?
المسؤول؟
You mean it wasn't an accident?!
لم تكن حادثةً إذاً؟
That's right. This was a murder made to look like an accident!
صحيح، كانت جريمة قتل زُيّفت لتبدو حادثة
What?!
!ماذا؟
Those earplugs were my first suspicion.
كانت سدّادات الأذن التي أشار لها كونان-كن هي ما أثار شبهتي بدايةً
That was the killer's oversight.
كانت غلطةً من القاتل
After knocking Saijo-san out with a chloroform-soaked rag,
...بعد تنويمه سايجو-سان بمنديل مبتلّ بالكلوروفورم
the killer plugged his ears
سدّ القاتل أُذنيه
with earplugs different from his own.
بسدّادات مختلفة عن سدّاداته المعتادة
As for the cap...
...كما غطاء الرأس
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
Was there any blood, hair, or signs
...أكانت هناك آثار دم أو شعر
of a strike on the diving platform?
أو علامة ارتطام على منصّة الغوص؟
No, nothing of the sort.
كلا، لا شيء من هذا
Wait, was the cap meant to fool us about that?!
!لحظة، أكان غطاء الرأس لخداعنا؟
Precisely.
تماماً
It was meant to make the poolside murder look like a diving accident.
رُتّب كلّ هذا ليجعل الجريمة تبدو حادثةً وقعت أثناء تمرين الغوص
M-My word!
!يـ-يا للهول
The killer then threw the removed clothes into Saijo-san's locker
رمى القاتل بعدها ثياب سايجو-سان المخلوعة في خزانته
and left... without locking it!
!وغادر، دون قفلها
But that's nothing more than circumstantial evidence, Mori-kun!
!لكنّ ذلك مجرد دليل ظرفيّ يا موري-كن
Besides, what about the witness?!
كما ماذا عن الشاهد؟
Actually, if that witness were to always look out the veranda
في الواقع، لو كان ذاك الشاهد ينظر من الشرفة دوماً
at a set time every day, that changes things substantially.
في وقت محدّد يومياً، فهذا يقلب الوضع
What?! The veranda, at a set time?!
ماذا؟ من الشرفة في وقت محدّد؟
What do you mean?!
ما قصدك؟
In short, the witness didn't coincidentally see it;
أي أنّ الشاهد لم يرَ بمحض الصدفة
he was made to see it!
!بل جُهّز له أن يرى
W-What?! Made to see his death?!
!ما-ماذا؟! جعله يرى موته؟
Don't tell me this was suicide?!
!أتقصد أنّه انتحار؟
If so, there'd be no need to turn off the lights and create a silhouette.
لم تكن هناك حاجة لإطفاء الأنوار وصنع صورة ظلّية في تلك الحالة
He turned the lights off?
أطفأ الأنوار؟
What for?
لمَ؟
He didn't want his face to be seen...
...لم يرد أن يُكشف وجهه
That's it! He saw someone completely different!
!فهمت! رأى الشاهد شخصاً مختلفاً
Yes. And it was that person who killed Saijo-san!
!صحيح، وذاك الشخص كان قاتل سايجو-سان
Kijima Hisashi-san.
كيجيما هيساشي-سان
You used to be a diver, but switched to swimming.
كنت غطّاس ارتفاع، لكنك انتقلت للسباحة
Might you have hated Saijo-san for taking your role as team captain?
ربما حملت ضغينةً تّجاه سايجو-سان لأخذه دور القائد منك؟
Competitive swimmers never swim without caps, correct?
السبّاحون التنافسيّون لا يسبحون دون غطاء رأس، أليس كذلك؟
Putting a cap on to avoid suspicion, even if no marks were left...
وضع غطاء رأس لتفادي الشبهة حتى ...لو لم تكن هناك آيّ آثار
That's something only a competitive swimmer would think of!
هذا أمرٌ لا يفكّر به سوى سبّاح تنافسيّ
So it was him?
كان هو إذاً؟
That's right.
صحيح
He killed Saijo-san and made it look like an accident!
!قتل سايجو-سان وجعلها تبدو حادثة
H-Hold on!
!ا-انتظر
You're going to accuse me based on some guess?!
!ستتهمني بناءً على مجرد تخمين؟
What proof do you have?!
ما الدليل لديك؟
Inspector.
حضرة المفتش
At the bottom of the platform stairs is a painting the witness made.
توجد لوحة رسمها الشاهد أسفل أدراج منصّة الغوص
Unwrap it and have a look.
افتح الغطاء وتفقدها رجاءً
T-This painting!
...هـ-هذه اللوحة
Saijo-kun...
...سايجو-كن
That was done while watching tonight's diving practice.
رُسمت أثناء مشاهدته تمرين الغوص المرتفع الليلة
Meaning... this is the killer?!
أي... هذا هو القاتل؟
Look closely.
أمعنوا النظر
Never mind that he cut the lights to show off his diving,
...بغض النظر عن إطفائه الأنوار للتباهي بغوصه
there was other definitive evidence that shone in the moonlight...
كان هناك دليل دامغ تلألأ بضوء القمر
The old man painted that faithfully to what he saw...
رسم المُسن ذاك بإخلاص كما رآه تماماً
Faithfully...
...بإخلاص
An earring!
!أقراط أذن
T-That can't be!
!لا-لا يمكن
One other thing--
...شيءٌ آخر
if the killer was an insider, he hasn't left yet!
إذا كان القاتل من الداخل، فلم يغادر بعد
Which means the murder weapon must be in this building somewhere.
ما يعني أنّ سلاح الجريمة مخفيّ في مكانٍ ما من المبنى حتماً
But why would he murder him over the role as team captain?
لكن لمَ قد يقتله لأخذه منصب القائد فقط؟
It probably wasn't about skill.
لم يكن الأمر حول المهارة غالباً
He blackmailed you, didn't he?
قام بابتزازك، أليس كذلك؟
T-That's right...
...صـ-صحيح
Half a year ago, I caused a motorcycle accident
قبل نصف عام، تسبّبتُ بحادث مروري بدرّاجتي
and severely injured my girlfriend who was sitting behind me.
وعرّضتُ حبيبتي التي كانت ورائي لإصابات بليغة
I dunno how he found out,
...لا أدري كيف اكتشف ذلك
but he threatened to tell the owner and the tournament committee!
لكنّه هددني بإخبار المالكة ولجنة المسابقة
So I used my health as a reason to give him my place as captain!
فاستعملتُ حالتي الصحيّة عذراً لإعطائه منصب القائد
But I couldn't forgive him!
!لكنّي لم أستطع مسامحته
He was no sportsman!
!لم يكن رياضياً بحقّ
He had to pay...
...لم أسامحه
It seems your mistake was making too perfect of a dive.
يبدو أنّ غلطتك كانت الغوص المثاليّ فوق الحاجة
It was a once-in-a-lifetime performance for me.
كان عرضاً لا يتكرر في العمر لي
I knew I should have,
أعرف أنّه كان عليّ السقوط
but I just couldn't lose my balance during it!
لكن لم أستطع إخلال توازني عمداً
My pride wouldn't let me...
...منعني كبريائي
A concrete block was later found in an office trash can.
عُثر على قالب إسمنتيّ في حاوية قمامة المكتب لاحقاً
Upon examination, it matched with Saijo-san's forehead injury,
طابقَ إصابة جبهة سايجو-سان بعد التحليل
and Kijima's fingerprints were found on it.
وُوجدت بصمات أصابع كيجيما عليه
Dad! Earth to Dad!
!أبي! أتسمعني يا أبي؟
Oh, crap! I forgot about him!
!تبّاً! نسيت أمره
Dad! We should get going now!
!أبي! علينا الرجوع
What a nice nap! Upsy-daisy!
!نمت جيّداً، وقوف
W-What am I doing up here?!
!ما-ماذا أفعل هنا؟
Oh no!
!كلا
Osaka's chief of police!
!قائد شرطة أوساكا
That's it! I figured out the locked room trick! And--
...فهمت, اكتشفتُ حيلة الغرفة المقفلة! كما
Conan-kun! Conan-kun, what's wrong?!
كونان-كن! كونان-كن، ما الخطب؟
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Diplomat Murder Case (Part 1).
(جريمة قتل الدبلوماسيّ (الجزء الأوّل
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Needle and Thread.
إبرة وخيط وفتحة قفل
Next episode Conan's rival appears.
!في الحلقة القادمة، يظهر مُنافس كونان
His name is Kojima Genta.
!واسمه كوجيما غينتا
No, it's not.
كلا